<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>info on Harry Callahan</title>
    <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/tags/info/</link>
    <description>Recent content in info on Harry Callahan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:37:40 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/tags/info/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Learned in cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/blog/blogb/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:37:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/blog/blogb/</guid>
      <description>I learned quite a much in this course. The course touched on automating the software testing, deployment and delivery and much more and I was happy to learn specifically about those subjects. For me Agile methods and theory are quite familiar as I have read about them in some extent but all additional information about actual practicalities of software development are intresting to me. But I really learn the best when I am actually doing something and aside from theory this course gave a chance to do a small project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This course cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/blog/bloga/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:37:40 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/blog/bloga/</guid>
      <description>I learned about this course from a friend and they recommended to take it. I reaserched about it a little bit from oodi and decided to start this course as it seemed really intresting. My motivation for taking this course and wanting to learn about DevOps is coming from my intrest in software development and computer science in general.
From the course I wanted to learn more about DevOps in practice and also really do somekind of project related to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2019 21:34:18 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aaltomcc.github.io/cs-ej4101-fall-2019-032-advanced/about/</guid>
      <description>My University journey started with electric engineering and while it is quite interesting once I was introduced to programming (altough it was C and I first flunked it) it really grasped me from the start. I realized that so much can be achieved via programming and that only your imagination is really the limit. The feeling of accomplishment when figuring out a unique solution to problem is quite extatic. And with coding comes the practises of coding: version control, efficient ways of development and deployment, testing the code and so on.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>